I look up to the stars
and reach for the sky.
I believe in tomorrow if we try.
Hey.
Come on, let's go, everybody.
Oh, we share the music.
We share the music.
Come on, let's go, baby, baby.
Oh, we share the one dream.
Come on, let's go, everybody.
Oh, we share the good times.
We share the good times.
Let's go, baby, baby, oh,
we share the one world?
It's hard to see for you and me!
Through the darkness
that is in this world.
So hard to see, but to believe!
In where we need to go.
Yes, you and me, it's true that we
Feel the rush brought on by this world.
Through head to feet, I feel the beat!
Getting me to walk on, oh yeah!
Share the music, no matter what.
Share the one dream, believe in yourself.
Share the good times, take my hand now.
Share the one world now!
I look up to the stars.
And reach for the sky.
No matter what!
I'll try no matter how high!
So let us go!
Beyond, far and wide!
I believe in tomorrow!
If we try high!
Yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah!
C'mon let's go everybody!
Oh we share the music!
C'mon let's go baby baby!
Oh we share the one world!
Oh as we chase we're being chased!
From the top we go on straight and wild!
We're on our way, I've got to say!
Hey, I want to share your style!
Now here it starts, so don't lose heart!
They're bound to lose to this flavor!
From boot to hood, I feel so good!
I will be free to be, oh yeah!
Share the music, even if I Share
the one dream, I know where you are!
Share the good times,
share the one world now!
I look up to the stars.
And reach for the sky.
No matter what!
I'll try no matter how high!
So let us go!
Beyond, far and wide!
I believe in tomorrow!
If we try!
I know that you are there!
Just on the other side!
Wait there for me!
Soon it will be you and I!
Then let us go!
Beyond, far and wide!
I believe in the one world!
If we try!
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!
Come on, let's go, everybody!
Oh, we share the music!
Come on, let's go, maybe, maybe!
Oh, we share the one world!
G-Galos!
Sorry, everybody.
Now that I've punched this guy,
there's going to be a Navy Admiral
coming here with a warship.
I'm just pissed I didn't
get to cut him down.
You beat me to it.
Hachi, hang in there.
Do you know how much
trouble you guys are in now?
Huh, that's just Luffy.
What can you do? Nothing.
Well, that's that.
I guess we're fighting.
First off, we gotta get
the key to Kami's collar.
It's probably backstage.
In the meantime, I'll
tend to Hachi's womb.
Jonas!
Dear brother, what have they done to you?
No one has ever laid a hand on
him, not even you, father You scum!
How dare you raise a hand to my son!
They angered the dragons Are they crazy?
Run for your lives!
Our righteous bloodline is directly
descended from the creators of this world.
You'll suffer for your dissonance!
No one gives a damn who you're related to.
That bastard kid St.
Roswell
Shoo!
Kunkase!
Hey!
Get a move on, Franky! Freak Amy!
I'm on it, you just leave it to me!
Seize them guards!
Capture those pirates!
They're responsible!
What kind of fool risks their
lives to protect a lousy fish?
Come back! Help!
Strong right!
Fresh fire!
Get back here!
No, leave me alone!
Armour in a storm? Not so smart.
Thunderbolt Chipsa!
Sorry.
You insist on defying us to the very end!
Why can't you just accept
your fate? Back down!
Our prank isn't for sale!
Summon the Navy Admiral and the warships!
We'll make those pirates suffer!
Some suicidal pirate
hit a celestial dragon!
There's a warship all the way
from the Navy headquarters!
36 caliber Phoenix!
Are you trying to kill us?
Kuma!
Kuma! Are you okay?
Those creeps didn't hurt
you, did they? I'm okay.
But you, that dragon shot you.
Nothing to worry about.
Come on, you ought to
know me better than that.
No measly bullet can keep me down.
Just hang in there, Kuma.
We're getting you out of here.
Right.
My, we're missing the party.
Look at the entrance.
It's completely blocked.
Goodness, what a quandary.
Well, let's crash right through.
You got it. What?
Can't we just tiptoe in instead? Let's go.
My allergy to auction
houses is glaring up.
More flying fish.
Thanks a lot.
Best of luck. The end.
Wing.
Take care buddy.
I'm off.
Clutch.
It's time for.
Feats of fancy.
Damn it.
Protect the mermaid.
She's my 500 mil future.
Maybe I should just stand up here.
and bravely pose a while longer.
You're going already.
Thanks for screwing up the
timing of my dramatic entrance!
These creatures will suffer my wrath.
I'll step the women as trophies and
starve the men for a life of slavery.
You crushed father!
Wait, that didn't hurt that much.
I'm so sorry, mister.
They took down St. Roswald, too.
You do know warships
are coming, don't you?
Usopp! Brooke! Robin!
Hey, you guys made it. About time.
Loopy, where's Kuma? Right there!
The thing is, we gotta get that
collar off her before we can go!
You'd better hurry!
The Navy is gonna show up any minute now!
I hate to tell you this, but the
Navy's already here, Straw Hat.
Who the hell are you?
What's with the bear?
Purple you picked a bad
time to revolt the navy's
had this place around it
since before the auction.
Even began they've got a
base in the archipelago
but i'm guessing they're
after someone please.
Leave in a calm and orderly
fashion it's all right
we have everything under
control how's it look?
Inside we've finished
evacuating all of the patrons
but the three celestial
dragons are still inside.
Then get him out of there!
Damn pirates!
You're not getting out of this alive!
I don't know who exactly
they're hoping to catch in here,
but I sincerely doubt they were expecting
someone to go and kick a
Celestial Dragon's ass.
That was a hell of a show you guys put on.
I'm impressed, Straw Hat.
Ah, you're Trafalgar Law.
Luffy, they're pirates just like us.
Huh?
Even the bear?
Please don't!
I beg you to stop, St. Shalria!
Could you maybe at least wait until
the merchandise has been paid for?
I beg of you, please stop. Have mercy!
I just want to be rich!
Enough, commoner! Silence!
Oh, crap! Kuma!
I'm trying to aim
What? St.
Shaulria
What did I tell you?
I know a ruckus when I hear one.
Looks like the auction's over.
I got the money I came here for.
Now guess I'll head back to the
gambling house and throw it all away.
You are one messed up old man.
You got locked up just
to steal some money?
That was the plan.
And if it had worked out, I was
going to rob whoever bought me, too.
But I guess it wasn't meant to be.
Oh, right, I forgot I'm out.
Time to find some more booze.
Now that I think about
it, I'd plan stinks.
Who the hell would spend money on
an old fart like me for a slave?
Oh boy, I didn't realize we
had such a captive audience.
Where did that old man
and the giant come from?
They were supposed to be merchandised
for the auction, but they were locked up.
How in the heck did they get out of there?
Their colors were gone.
There's no way they could
have gotten them off.
What do we do?
How should I know?
It's not our job to capture slaves,
and we've got no chance going
up against an unshackled giant.
R-Reilly?
Wait, E-Reilly?
The coding mechanic?
Which one is it?
Hey, is that you, Hachi? It sure is.
I'll be damned.
So, pal, what are you doing here?
Did someone hurt you?
No, no, don't speak.
Save your energy.
I see now, plain as day,
a terrible situation.
Well, you were fighting for what
you believe is right, Hachi.
You must be the good
folks who stood by him.
All right.
Is he...
no way?
What? But how?
What did you do to them?
Okay, who is this guy?
That Straw Hat you wear it suits a
fearless man like yourself quite well.
Yes I wanted to meet you Monkey D Luffy.
This is bad news the whole town no
the whole archipelago's in trouble.
Stride, Luffy just beat the
crap out of a celestial dragon.
It happened at the auction
house over on Grove No.
1. No way.
Apparently, Captain Kidd and
Captain Law are there, too.
That stupid Straw Hat.
What the hell was he thinking?
Doesn't he know they're
going to send an admiral
over from Navy headquarters
with a battleship?
Has our ship been coated yet?
Finished yesterday.
Then we set sail immediately.
I'm not going to sit around
waiting for an admiral to show up.
Yes, sir.
Guess they're dumbass captains an
even bigger dumbass than I thought.
If I run into them in the new
world, they're dead! Dead!
Causing trouble with Navy headquarters
with the new world right in their sights.
Those Straw Hats are certainly
audacious, if nothing else.
Make preparations to set sail quickly.
Yes, sir, Captain Drake.
Right away.
Whoever shows up, it can't be good news.
Given the situation, I doubt
they'll bother to arrest all of us.
After all, Straw Hat's the one they want.
And I kind of want to see what
an animal is like in action.
What, you're kidding me?
We gotta get the hell
out of here now, Apu!
Captain Hawkins, please.
It's dangerous here.
Let's set sail immediately.
Calm yourself.
After all, I am not
destined to die on this day.
That brat again.
It's just one thing after another.
What is wrong with that whole family?
They're crazy.
Reports indicate that along
with the Straw Hat crew,
Captain Eustass Kidd and
Trafalgar Law are also present.
With a total of 13 pirates
with bounties confirmed,
five being rookies
worth over $100 million.
Of them, the key offender
appears to be Monkey D.
Luffy, who assaulted a celestial dragon.
We've lost all contact with the
guards at the human shop, uh,
I mean the employment office.
Given the conditions reported from that
area, they've most likely been subdued.
Whatever the case,
the act of taking three celestial dragons
hostage is a vile and
unprecedented transgression.
Have they made any demands? No, sir.
None at the moment.
Whatever the case may be, we'll
need to take immediate action.
After all, the world nobles
are the victims here, right?
But don't worry.
I'll take care of it myself.
I won't be gone for long.
Damn it, this is no laughing matter.
Please, I need you, Mr. Doflamingo.
Roswald and his family are
going to come after us.
They'll never stand for this.
And even worse, our shop's lost
every last bit of its credibility.
We're ruined you hear me, please.
You've got to take care of this mess.
Oh Get a grip.
Human trafficking is so
yesterday's news you fool!
It's all about the smiles now
you understand now listen?
I'm giving the shop to you disco.
You're on your own now.
So don't be calling me anymore
What you're just going to abandon
me during our worst crisis ever?
Shut up.
Geez, you're annoying.
The hell out of me while you sit there
blaming me for your own misfortune!
A new era continues to draw ever closer.
I've been ordered.
Well, all of us actually have
been ordered into active duty by
the Navy.
I bet you're wondering
what's about to happen.
Well, let me tell you that.
Would be the Whitebeard Pirates
versus the seven warlords of the sea?
Everyone, get as far away
from this area as possible!
These people are dangerous.
This is for your own good!
But the slave I'm on is
still trapped inside.
Any news?
Have the mortars arrived yet?
Yes, sir, most of them anyway.
They're being set up as we speak.
Any updates from HQ?
Admiral Kizaru's on his way, sir, but
they're bringing in the special vanguard.
What?
You're kidding me,
they're coming? Yes, sir.
At least, that's what I was told.
Whoa, now hold on. Are you crazy?
You can't, it'll explode.
Yeah, it's true!
We've seen it happen before!
Stop!
You'll hurt her!
Bad idea!
Very bad idea!
It'll be alright, just don't flinch.
I have no idea what kind of
power that guy used earlier.
Where's Franky with that key?
What's he doing?
I'm telling you, just wait!
This is a big mistake!
He set it off! It's gonna blow!
What are we gonna do?
GAMY!
Don't scare me like that.
I thought I was too late.
Went to all the trouble to find the key
and you don't even need the damn thing.
It's off.
Kuma!
Oh, thank goodness!
What the hell?
How'd you do that?
Look, these weren't
easy to find, you know?
Oh, nicely done.
Better luck next time, then.
Here, carrier.
Kuma, you're safe now.
Nothing to worry about.
How did you...?
Uh, thank you.
What's going on here?
Look, man, I appreciate the
help, but seriously, who are you?
What the?
How did he do that?
That old geezer's got
some kind of freaky power!
Just who is he anyway?
And where did he come from?
Hey, today's your lucky day.
All the fires took off.
Unless you like being a slave, I'd
get out of here while you still can.
Boom!
That geezer took out all these
guards at once, like by himself.
He must know how to use magic.
Maybe he's a sorcerer.
Well, whatever he is, he's powerful.
And he said something
about Luffy's hat, too.
That Straw Hat you wear, it suits a
fearless man like yourself quite well.
Yes, I've wanted to meet you.
Monkey D. Luffy.
How do you know him, Luffy?
I haven't even met him, he just said!
I think he used something called Haki.
I've heard of it, but I've
never seen it used before.
Oh, I'm sorry about that, everyone.
I didn't realize there were
other pirates here as well.
You must all be quite strong to withstand
something like that with no trouble.
Well, well, I never expected
to meet such a big shot here!
Dark King Silver's Ray,
you're a legend, old man.
What are you doing in a place like this?
On these islands, I'm just
Ray, the coding craftsman.
Don't go around calling
me that other name.
I'm retired now.
I just want a quiet and peaceful life.
Looks like you'll live, Hachi?
What did I tell you about
walking around this archipelago?
You gotta be more careful.
I know, I'm sorry.
Thank you, for everything!
I appreciate you saving my friend here.?
So what was that about
you wanting to meet me?
Hmm, let's save that for later.
First, we need to get out of here!
They've got us cornered
from every angle, boss?
Got a plan?
Tested, one, two.
All right, you criminals!
Release the Roswa family.
An admiral will be arriving shortly.
I recommend you surrender immediately.
And don't blame us for
whatever happens, you rookies!
Come on, we're just innocent bystanders.
Why is the Navy treating
us like accomplices?
On the upside, I got to see Straw
Hat Luffy do something crazy,
so no complaints there.
Still, I'd rather avoid
fighting an admiral.
Sure.
But if you're expecting me to help,
I've used my power enough today.
It's all up to you now.
It'll be hard for me to stay
if the Navy discovers who I am.
I don't need a senior
citizen to fight for me.
The longer we wait, the worse it'll get.
I'm out of here.
If you babies can't handle a few Marines,
then sit here while I show you how
a real man takes care of things.
Look, I already told you,
I'm gonna do it! Shut up!
I'm gonna take care of them!
Back off, will ya?
I said I got it.
Beat it, you two.
Leave this to me.
You can't get lost.
I'm gonna do it.
If you hear me, just go back inside.
You can't tell me what to do.
Why don't you settle down?
Why don't you get out of my face?
Somebody should muzzle both of you.
Settle.
All right.
Go back inside, guys.
Aren't you listening?
I told you two to go back inside first.
I got this.
Try to boss me around like that again.
You'll be the first when
I cut down, Eustass.
Get ready.
I'll handle this by myself.
All three have bounties
way over a hundred million
Do all captains act like children
or just those idiots? Hey,
it's gonna get ugly out
there Let's use this
chance to escape waiting
around is just plain crazy
Hodgin, thank you.
I'm sorry for causing you so much trouble.
Oh, come on.
Never mind all that I'm just
glad that you're all right.
Follow them.
Try to break through in one shot
That sounds like a plan if we
happen to get separated in the chaos
Let's meet up at Grove number 13.
I know my way around.
Grove 13, got it.
You'll be lucky if you find
your way out of the building!
Mr.
Giant, what about you?
All of us were on the
verge of becoming slaves.
Now I'm going to escape
somewhere with them.
Very well.
Try not to draw attention
to yourself, okay?
Old man, Straw Hat, and your crew!
I will repay the favor
if we ever meet again!
Thanks for everything!
Sure, it was no problem! Huh?
You're taking credit? Mortars! Fire!
Balloons!
Repel!
Now room.
Hey, what's up with this
circle bubble thing?
And shambles.
You killed me!
Wait, what?